<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>phones on Kugadi</title>
    <link>https://www.kugadi.com/tags/phones/</link>
    <description>Recent content in phones on Kugadi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2016 13:55:56 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.kugadi.com/tags/phones/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Choosing the Right Smartphones for Your Security Business</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2016/04/13/choosing-the-right-smartphones-for-your-security-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2016 13:55:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2016/04/13/choosing-the-right-smartphones-for-your-security-business/</guid>
      <description>It is becoming clear that more and more security officers are carrying a smartphone as part of their standard equipment. This sparks the debate regarding whether it is best to supply your employees with iPhones or Android phones. While there are certainly no shortage of articles that generically discuss the merits of each, for example hereand here, I thought I would look at some of the more specific needs of the contract security market as it pertains to choosing iPhones or Androids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What to Expect from Mobile Apps in the Security Industry</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2016/01/22/what-to-expect-from-mobile-apps-in-the-security-industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 16:43:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2016/01/22/what-to-expect-from-mobile-apps-in-the-security-industry/</guid>
      <description>In the Security Newsdesk article, Physical Security and Cyber Security Predictions for 2016, one of the key predictions is that “Mobility Matters.” The article infers that smartphone applications are becoming more and more important in the general operations of security companies. In fact, they go so far as to say that “customers are redefining their operations around mobility and demanding that it flexes to their needs.” So, I thought I would take a look at what a mobile app can do for a guard company and some ideas of just what you need to consider if you want to start using one in your company.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>