<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kugadi - Guard Tour System Made Easy on Kugadi</title>
    <link>https://www.kugadi.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kugadi - Guard Tour System Made Easy on Kugadi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 14:51:11 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.kugadi.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kugadi - About Us</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 14:21:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/about-us/</guid>
      <description>About Kugadi Kugadi is a Miami, FL based company focused on using technology to solve real world problems. It was founded in 2015 by Gavin Heale, Brendon Whateley and Todd Shimizu. All three are veterans of multiple high tech companies with decades of collective experience in this space. It has a head office in Miami, FL and a Silicon Valley office in Fremont, CA.
Kugadi was formed after seeing a real market need.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kugadi - FAQ</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 14:19:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/faq/</guid>
      <description>.question { color: #666; } .answer { color: #555; }  Frequently Asked Questions  Who is Kugadi?   Kugadi is a Miami, FL based company that produces a smartphone app based Guard Tour System. This can be used by any company that has security guards to greatly modernize their operations and streamline their business.    What is a Guard Tour System?   A guard tour system is a system that uses a device, often known as a wand or a pipe, or smartphone app to track the activities of a security guard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security Patrol System Demo</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/security-patrol-system-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 15:22:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/security-patrol-system-demo/</guid>
      <description>(888) 236-5031   --  (888) 236-5031    Security Patrol System  Know Where Your Officers are 100% of the Time   Upgrade your business with our Guard Tour System Our total focus is one making your business easier to run and more profitable. Our Guard Tour System is cloud based and requires no costly setup and maintenance. Your officers will add much more value as they no longer need as much supervision and training.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guard Patrol System Demo</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/guard-patrol-system-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 15:22:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/guard-patrol-system-demo/</guid>
      <description>(888) 236-5031   --  (888) 236-5031    Guard Patrol System  Know Where Your Officers are 100% of the Time   Upgrade your business with our Guard Tour System Our total focus is one making your business easier to run and more profitable. Our Guard Tour System is cloud based and requires no costly setup and maintenance. Your officers will add much more value as they no longer need as much supervision and training.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Analytics to get new customers for your Security Company</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2019/12/11/using-analytics-to-get-new-customers-for-your-security-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 15:26:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2019/12/11/using-analytics-to-get-new-customers-for-your-security-company/</guid>
      <description>At the beginning of this year, one of our main customers made us a specific request: They needed to know how many parking violations were issued by their security officers during the previous month in one particular property. This property is a residential building that does not have a visitor&amp;rsquo;s parking, so visitors constantly park inappropriately creating great discomfort in the residents of the building.
We immediately checked our system and informed the customer that only during the previous month, their officers had generated 193 property violations in the building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great Customizable Forms - Designing with Purpose</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2019/10/30/great-customizable-forms-designing-with-purpose/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 12:28:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2019/10/30/great-customizable-forms-designing-with-purpose/</guid>
      <description>Working as a software engineer at Kugadi, we are always looking at developing tools to improve the customer experience and at the same time provide a workflow that is both intuitive and easy to use. We recognize that one size does not fit all but how do we balance ease of use with a fully flexible solution? My current project is developing a customizable form for our clients’ reports and the Officer Assist app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guard Tour Patrol System Demo</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/guard-tour-patrol-system-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 17:36:53 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/guard-tour-patrol-system-demo/</guid>
      <description>(888) 236-5031   --  (888) 236-5031    Guard Tour Patrol System  Know Where Your Officers are 100% of the Time   Upgrade your business with our Guard Tour System Our total focus is one making your business easier to run and more profitable. Our Guard Tour System is cloud based and requires no costly setup and maintenance. Your officers will add much more value as they no longer need as much supervision and training.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kugadi - Activity Reports</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/activity-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 17:00:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/activity-report/</guid>
      <description>Simple Activity Reports  Automated Daily Activity Reports make you more Efficient   Automated Email Reporting   Stop spending time on paper reports with Kugadi’s automated, real-time daily activity reports. Through timely and relevant emails, your team and clients will know the guard’s performance at all times.
Have happy customers by making sure they have all the detail they want in each report. You can include pictures taken while the guard was on tour and even maps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You Request Demo</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/thank-you-request-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 14:23:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/thank-you-request-demo/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for Requesting a Demo Please expect an email in the near future where we will schedule a time to show you our system
For more details please go to our main website by clicking here
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Request Demo</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/request-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 14:11:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/request-demo/</guid>
      <description>LET US CONVINCE YOU IN JUST 7 MINUTES Don’t fill this out if you&#39;re human:        REQUEST A DEMO    LET US CONVINCE YOU IN JUST 7 MINUTES Don’t fill this out if you&#39;re human:    REQUEST A DEMO   CLICK TO CALL   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You Inline Demo</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/thank-you-inline-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 13:41:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/thank-you-inline-demo/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for Requesting a Demo Please expect an email in the near future where we will schedule a time to show you our system
For more details please go to our main website by clicking here
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You Tracking Demo</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/thank-you-tracking-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 13:41:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/thank-you-tracking-demo/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for Requesting a Demo Please expect an email in the near future where we will schedule a time to show you our system
For more details please go to our main website by clicking here
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 15:43:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY AGREEMENT
Kugadi Inc, (Kugadi), is committed to keeping any and all personal information collected of those individuals that visit our website and make use of our online facilities and services accurate, confidential, secure and private. Our privacy policy has been designed and created to ensure those affiliated with Kugadi Inc of our commitment and realization of our obligation not only to meet but to exceed most existing privacy standards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guard Tour System Demo</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/guard-tour-system-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 10:43:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/guard-tour-system-demo/</guid>
      <description>(888) 236-5031   --  (888) 236-5031    Guard Tour System  Know Where Your Officers are 100% of the Time   Upgrade your business with our Guard Tour System Our total focus is one making your business easier to run and more profitable. Our Guard Tour System is cloud based and requires no costly setup and maintenance. Your officers will add much more value as they no longer need as much supervision and training.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guard Tracking Demo</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/guard-tracking-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 10:43:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/guard-tracking-demo/</guid>
      <description>(888) 236-5031   --  (888) 236-5031    Guard Tracking System  Track Your Officers 100% of the Time   Upgrade your business with our Guard Tour System Our total focus is one making your business easier to run and more profitable. Our Guard Tour System is cloud based and requires no costly setup and maintenance. Your officers will add much more value as they no longer need as much supervision and training.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Kugadi</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/why-kugadi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 11:54:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/why-kugadi/</guid>
      <description>Why Kugadi  Stop being hired as an scapegoat. Prove your guards do an excellent job.   Great Sales Tool for Your Business   Close new prospects, and retain the clients you already have:
 Easily provide accountability of your services. Show how your patrols add value. Build trust with transparency and efficiency.  Kugadi’s Dispatch System makes your clients feel confident and safe as they stay informed with 24/7 access to their personalized customer portal and electronic daily activity reports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kugadi - Guard Tracking</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/guard-tracking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 15:11:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/guard-tracking/</guid>
      <description>Guard Tracking  Track your Guards, no more need for Supervision on site.   GPS Guard Tracking   Know who’s on duty and where they are, 100% of the time.
Understand not only your officer’s precise physical location right now but also where they have been any time in the past. Kugadi’s GPS guard tracking feature lets you pinpoint any incident with precision and confidence.
Improve efficiency, prevent danger, and provide accurate reporting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kugadi - Guard Management</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/guard-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 16:56:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/guard-management/</guid>
      <description>Security Guard Management  Have insights about your officers you never had before.   Time and Attendance Monitoring   In a legally ever more complicated world, it’s critical that you prove exactly what normal hours, overtime hours and breaks you employees work. No more building complicated spreadsheets to track time. Our Guard Tour System take’s care of this simply and transparently.
 Automated Daily Activity Reports   Everything that your officer does during his tour can be used to automatically generate a daily activity report.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Get New Accounts for your Security Guard Company</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2018/05/30/get-new-accounts-security-guard-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 16:05:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2018/05/30/get-new-accounts-security-guard-company/</guid>
      <description>When we speak to owners and managers of contract security companies, many of them complain about the difficulty of getting new business. A few, however, seem to find it much easier. I going to write about some of the lessons we have learned after dealing with many companies in the industry.
Why it’s Hard to Get New Accounts You really have two choices for new business. You are going to either find a building or organization that does not currently have security services, or you are going to try displace another company that is already providing services to your prospect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Beat the Competition for Contract Security Guard Companies</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2018/04/30/beat-competition-contract-security-guard-companies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 17:19:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2018/04/30/beat-competition-contract-security-guard-companies/</guid>
      <description>There are a lot of articles on the web on how to beat your competition, but I thought I would try to look more specifically at the contract security guard industry. I hope you will find this thought provoking and I would love to get any feedback.
Competition is Good – But You Need to Beat It The first thing to remember about competition is that it is good. If you are in a market with a lot of competition, that means there is a need for your product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workforce Management, a Benefit to Everyone Involved</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2018/03/01/workforce-management-benefit-everyone-involved/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 12:45:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2018/03/01/workforce-management-benefit-everyone-involved/</guid>
      <description>As we come into 2018, I got to thinking about just how much has changed over the last few years and how much it could continue to change. One of the largest drivers I have seen is the continued automation of many jobs that traditionally did not really have any technical component. I am talking about jobs like security officer, cleaner, maintenance engineer and even home care worker.
Today, customers are no longer assuming that these people are doing their jobs well but rather looking for evidence in the form of some kind of automated reports and this is where Workforce Management comes in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Views from the Field – Real World Security Operations</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2017/10/26/real-world-security-operations/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 13:23:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2017/10/26/real-world-security-operations/</guid>
      <description>Last week, we have the good fortune to talk to Jorge Fernandez, Director of Special Services at Admiral Security Services about some real world security operations where our guard tour system is used. We got some useful insights from the conversation and I thought I would share them with you.
The Value of a Guard Tour System We always wonder where our customers get the greatest value from our products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Artificial Intelligence will Affect the Physical Security Industry</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2017/08/28/artificial-intelligence-physical-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 13:28:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2017/08/28/artificial-intelligence-physical-security/</guid>
      <description>Artificial Intelligence, or Machine Learning as it is commonly referred to these days, is one of the hottest technologies that is changing the world today. It has been identified as an Exponential Technology by Salim Ismail of Singularity University which means it is a technology for which performance relative to cost and size is doubling every one to two years.
This incredible level of growth has got me thinking how it will affect Workforce Management systems like Guard Tour Systems as well as the physical security industry as a whole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GPS Guard Tracking and the Modern Security Company</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2017/08/07/gps-guard-tracking-modern-security-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 13:35:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2017/08/07/gps-guard-tracking-modern-security-company/</guid>
      <description>What’s your worst nightmare as the owner of a contract security guard company? I imagine it might have something to do with your biggest client phoning you up at 3 a.m. to scream at you about a huge security breach and to tell you your guards are nowhere to be seen. So how do you know if your guards are at their posts and following post order rather than down at the coffee shop getting a quick fix?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Makes a Great Guard Tour System?</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2016/06/20/what-makes-a-great-guard-tour-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2016 13:47:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2016/06/20/what-makes-a-great-guard-tour-system/</guid>
      <description>As with many industries, the contract security guard industry has to keep up with the times and that means taking advantage of the latest technology. Part of that may include finding the right guard tour system to track and report on the movement of your security officers when they are on patrol.
In this article I am going to look at some detail about why you need one and what you would expect from this kind of system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Choosing the Right Smartphones for Your Security Business</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2016/04/13/choosing-the-right-smartphones-for-your-security-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2016 13:55:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2016/04/13/choosing-the-right-smartphones-for-your-security-business/</guid>
      <description>It is becoming clear that more and more security officers are carrying a smartphone as part of their standard equipment. This sparks the debate regarding whether it is best to supply your employees with iPhones or Android phones. While there are certainly no shortage of articles that generically discuss the merits of each, for example hereand here, I thought I would look at some of the more specific needs of the contract security market as it pertains to choosing iPhones or Androids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Effective Reporting for Physical Security</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2016/03/16/effective-reporting-for-physical-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2016 14:01:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2016/03/16/effective-reporting-for-physical-security/</guid>
      <description>For most in the physical security industry, client reporting means simply sending your officer’s daily activity report (DAR) to your customer. While this is a good start, we have observed that reporting in this way, does not give the customer everything they need and want. A more flexible approach to reporting is needed to keep customer satisfaction high. Here are some ideas to help you improve your business.
What Information Customers Want Remember that every customer is different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What to Expect from Mobile Apps in the Security Industry</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2016/01/22/what-to-expect-from-mobile-apps-in-the-security-industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 16:43:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2016/01/22/what-to-expect-from-mobile-apps-in-the-security-industry/</guid>
      <description>In the Security Newsdesk article, Physical Security and Cyber Security Predictions for 2016, one of the key predictions is that “Mobility Matters.” The article infers that smartphone applications are becoming more and more important in the general operations of security companies. In fact, they go so far as to say that “customers are redefining their operations around mobility and demanding that it flexes to their needs.” So, I thought I would take a look at what a mobile app can do for a guard company and some ideas of just what you need to consider if you want to start using one in your company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are Your Security Services Effectively Leveraging Technology?</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2016/01/08/are-your-security-services-effectively-leveraging-technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2016 16:59:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2016/01/08/are-your-security-services-effectively-leveraging-technology/</guid>
      <description>During our consulting work in the contract security industry, we are often asked about how to make companies more competitive and more efficient. One of the areas we have discovered that makes a big impact on the efficiency and competitive positioning of companies selling or using security services is the workflow followed by their security guards. We find that the security companies with the most efficient services are using an “automated guard workflow”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technologies for Tracking Security Guards</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2015/12/15/technologies-for-tracking-security-guards/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 17:17:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2015/12/15/technologies-for-tracking-security-guards/</guid>
      <description>Technology is changing our world. But which technologies are right for you, your business and your customers? In this article, I am going to explore the advantages and challenges associated with common technologies used in smartphone based guard tour systems for tracking security officer locations and activity.
Global Positioning System (GPS) The technology that springs to mind when discussing tracking, smartphones and maps is GPS. If you own a smart phone, you are familiar with GPS because of applications like Google Maps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Accurate Is Your Smartphone Gps</title>
      <link>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2015/12/09/how-accurate-is-your-smartphone-gps/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2015 17:29:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2015/12/09/how-accurate-is-your-smartphone-gps/</guid>
      <description>As part of Officer Assist, our Android based guard tour system, we track the movement of security guards using the phones GPS location. We have collected hundred’s of millions of individual fixes and so we thought it would be interesting to try and find the accuracy of each fix and of phone based GPS in general. What we found may surprise you!
Getting the Raw Data Fortunately for us, the Location API in Android gives us an accuracy figure for each position (see http://developer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>