<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>marketing on Kugadi</title><link>https://www.kugadi.com/tags/marketing/</link><description>Recent content in marketing on Kugadi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 16:05:26 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.kugadi.com/tags/marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to Get New Accounts for your Security Guard Company</title><link>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2018/05/30/get-new-accounts-security-guard-company/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 16:05:26 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2018/05/30/get-new-accounts-security-guard-company/</guid><description>When we speak to owners and managers of contract security companies, many of them complain about the difficulty of getting new business. A few, however, seem to find it much easier. I going to write about some of the lessons we have learned after dealing with many companies in the industry.
Why it’s Hard to Get New Accounts You really have two choices for new business. You are going to either find a building or organization that does not currently have security services, or you are going to try displace another company that is already providing services to your prospect.</description></item><item><title>How to Beat the Competition for Contract Security Guard Companies</title><link>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2018/04/30/beat-competition-contract-security-guard-companies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 17:19:23 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2018/04/30/beat-competition-contract-security-guard-companies/</guid><description>There are a lot of articles on the web on how to beat your competition, but I thought I would try to look more specifically at the contract security guard industry. I hope you will find this thought provoking and I would love to get any feedback.
Competition is Good – But You Need to Beat It The first thing to remember about competition is that it is good. If you are in a market with a lot of competition, that means there is a need for your product.</description></item></channel></rss>