<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>physical security on Kugadi</title><link>https://www.kugadi.com/tags/physical-security/</link><description>Recent content in physical security on Kugadi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 16:05:26 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.kugadi.com/tags/physical-security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to Get New Accounts for your Security Guard Company</title><link>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2018/05/30/get-new-accounts-security-guard-company/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 16:05:26 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2018/05/30/get-new-accounts-security-guard-company/</guid><description>When we speak to owners and managers of contract security companies, many of them complain about the difficulty of getting new business. A few, however, seem to find it much easier. I going to write about some of the lessons we have learned after dealing with many companies in the industry.
Why it’s Hard to Get New Accounts You really have two choices for new business. You are going to either find a building or organization that does not currently have security services, or you are going to try displace another company that is already providing services to your prospect.</description></item><item><title>How to Beat the Competition for Contract Security Guard Companies</title><link>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2018/04/30/beat-competition-contract-security-guard-companies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 17:19:23 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2018/04/30/beat-competition-contract-security-guard-companies/</guid><description>There are a lot of articles on the web on how to beat your competition, but I thought I would try to look more specifically at the contract security guard industry. I hope you will find this thought provoking and I would love to get any feedback.
Competition is Good – But You Need to Beat It The first thing to remember about competition is that it is good. If you are in a market with a lot of competition, that means there is a need for your product.</description></item><item><title>How Artificial Intelligence will Affect the Physical Security Industry</title><link>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2017/08/28/artificial-intelligence-physical-security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 13:28:15 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2017/08/28/artificial-intelligence-physical-security/</guid><description>Artificial Intelligence, or Machine Learning as it is commonly referred to these days, is one of the hottest technologies that is changing the world today. It has been identified as an Exponential Technology by Salim Ismail of Singularity University which means it is a technology for which performance relative to cost and size is doubling every one to two years.
This incredible level of growth has got me thinking how it will affect Workforce Management systems like Guard Tour Systems as well as the physical security industry as a whole.</description></item><item><title>GPS Guard Tracking and the Modern Security Company</title><link>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2017/08/07/gps-guard-tracking-modern-security-company/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 13:35:45 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2017/08/07/gps-guard-tracking-modern-security-company/</guid><description>What’s your worst nightmare as the owner of a contract security guard company? I imagine it might have something to do with your biggest client phoning you up at 3 a.m. to scream at you about a huge security breach and to tell you your guards are nowhere to be seen. So how do you know if your guards are at their posts and following post order rather than down at the coffee shop getting a quick fix?</description></item><item><title>Are Your Security Services Effectively Leveraging Technology?</title><link>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2016/01/08/are-your-security-services-effectively-leveraging-technology/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2016 16:59:35 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://www.kugadi.com/blog/2016/01/08/are-your-security-services-effectively-leveraging-technology/</guid><description>During our consulting work in the contract security industry, we are often asked about how to make companies more competitive and more efficient. One of the areas we have discovered that makes a big impact on the efficiency and competitive positioning of companies selling or using security services is the workflow followed by their security guards. We find that the security companies with the most efficient services are using an “automated guard workflow”.</description></item></channel></rss>